# **MARIANA DAL CAROBO**

# VISUAL DESIGNER & ILLUSTRATOR

MARIANADALC.COM

**\( 083 875 9910** 

Hey, my name is Mariana and I'm a Visual Designer and Illustrator from Brazil, currently living in Dublin. I have more than five years of experience with both Graphic and Digital Design, working in Advertising and Design agencies in the past.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

- ILUSTRAMARI
  Freelance Illustrator (2017-2018)
- DZ STUDIO

Visual Designer (2015-2017)

Branding, User interface, Illustration, Prototyping, Wireframing, Research and Concept development for online presence.

DEZ PROPAGANDA

Junior Designer (2014-2015)

User interface, Branding, Illustration, Creative concept development.

GOYA

Junior Designer (2013-2014)

User interface, Branding, Illustration, Creative concept development.

DZ STUDIO

Design Intern (2012-2013)

Branding and Creative concept development.

#### **SKILLS**

Graphic and Digital Design, Illustration, Branding, User Interface, Creative concept development.

Adobe Creative Suit (Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign), Sketch, Microsoft Office and Keynote.

## **EDUCATION**

• GRAPHIC DESIGN DEGREE

UniRitter Laureate International Universities (2010-2015)

# **LANGUAGES**

- PORTUGUESE / Native
- ENGLISH / Advanced

## HOBBIES

Illustration, Film Photography, Animated movies and Video Games.